thetappingsolution.com 2019-06-30

# Privacy Policy - The Tapping Solution

The following Privacy Policy governs the online information collection practices of The Tapping Solution, LLC. (“TTS” “we” or “us”). Specifically, it outlines the types of information that we gather about you while you are using TheTappingSolution.com (the “Site”) or any of our other websites, and the ways in which we use this information.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. By visiting and using the Site, you agree that your use of our Site, and any dispute over privacy, is governed by this Privacy Policy. Because the Web is an evolving medium, we may need to change our Privacy Policy at some point in the future, in which case we’ll post the changes to this Privacy Policy on this website and update the Effective Date of the policy to reflect the date of the changes. By continuing to use the Site after we post any such changes, you accept the Privacy Policy as modified.

### **The Most Important Part…**

Above all, it’s important that you know that we will always respect your privacy, your email address, and the information you give us. We never sell, trade, or abuse any information you submit to us.  And if you ever want to stop receiving emails from us, we make it as easy as possible to stop receiving our regular communications, no questions asked.

### **Collection of your Personal Information**

Visitors to TheTappingSolution.com may be asked to share personally identifiable information, such as their e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number, and billing information (such as a credit card number when purchasing a product).  When you sign up for our email newsletter or purchase one of our products or services, you’ll be receiving relevant information about how to use EFT, Tapping, and other personal development techniques and information, along with receiving invites to our online events and programs.  The personal information collected is used to provide you with this personal development information, as well as to provide you with a customized experience as you use our Products and Services.

### **How to Stop Receiving Information From Us At Any Time (i.e., How to “Unsubscribe”)**

If you wish to stop receiving emails from us, you may unsubscribe at any time using the link provided at the bottom of all our emails. But if you’re still receiving emails from us, don’t worry, our Customer Service Team will be there for you!  Just email support at contact@thetappingsolution.com.  The image below will show you where the unsubscribe button shows up on the bottom of your emails:

### **Will My Information Ever Be Shared?**

We never rent or sell your information with anybody, ever, period!  We deeply value our relationship with you.  Our goal is to provide you valuable information to dramatically improve your life.  And we definitely don’t think that you getting junk email would help!  That’s why we keep your information safe and make it easy to unsubscribe.

The only time that we share information is with trusted partners (see “Trusted Partners” section below) for the purposes of fulfillment of services.  For example, our fulfillment house needs mailing information in order to be able to ship you a product you ordered, etc.

### **Computer Hardware and Software Information**

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by the systems used by TheTappingSolution.com. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by TheTappingSolution.com to ensure that the information we provide is working properly across all platforms, as well for the general operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the TheTappingSolution.com Web site to improve our services to you.

### **Sharing on Public Blog Comments**

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through any of TheTappingSolution.com blogs by commenting, this information may be collected and used by others.  We encourage you not to ever share your email address or any other private information publicly when commenting.

### **Affiliated Web Sites**

From time to time, TheTappingSolution.com may share resources such as books, articles or other free or paid information from other websites.  If you choose to visit any of these websites, we encourage you to review the privacy statements of those Web sites you choose to link to from TheTappingSolution.com so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information.

TheTappingSolution.com is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the TheTappingSolution.com and TheTappingSolution.com family of Web sites.

### **Trusted Partners**

In order to deliver our emails, ship any products you order, provide customer support and generally provide services to you, TheTappingSolution.com may share data with trusted partners.  All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to TheTappingSolution.com, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

TheTappingSolution.com does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

TheTappingSolution.com keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within TheTappingSolution.com.  We do this in order to determine which TheTappingSolution.com services are the most popular. This data is at times also used to deliver customized content and advertising within TheTappingSolution.com to customers whose actions indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.  
  
TheTappingSolution.com Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on TheTappingSolution.com or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of TheTappingSolution.com; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of TheTappingSolution.com, or the public.

### **Use of Cookies**

The TheTappingSolution.com Web site uses a very common practice of using “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience (Many websites use cookies and you can easily identify them in any browser). A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize TheTappingSolution.com pages, or register with TheTappingSolution.com site or services, a cookie helps TheTappingSolution.com to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same TheTappingSolution.com Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the TheTappingSolution.com features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the TheTappingSolution.com services or Web sites you visit.

### **General Data Privacy Regulation (GDPR)**

The GDPR takes effect on May 25, 2018, and is intended to protect the data of European Union (EU) citizens.

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA) or are accessing this site from within the EEA, you may have the right to request: access to, correction of, deletion of; portability of; and restriction or objection to processing, of your personal data, from us. This includes the “right to be forgotten.”

To make any of these requests, please contact our GDPR contact at [gdpr@thetappingsolution.com](mailto:gdpr@thetappingsolution.com).

### **Children’s Privacy Statement**

This children’s privacy statement explains our practices with respect to the online collection and use of personal information from children under the age of thirteen and provides important information regarding their rights under federal law with respect to such information.

  * This Site is not directed to children under the age of thirteen and we do NOT knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen as part of the Site. We screen users who wish to provide personal information in order to prevent users under the age of thirteen from providing such information. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personally identifiable information from a user under the age of thirteen as part of the Site, we will delete such information from our records. If we change our practices in the future, we will obtain prior, verifiable parental consent before collecting any personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen as part of the Site.
  * Because we do not collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen as part of the Site, we also do NOT knowingly distribute such information to third parties.
  * We do NOT knowingly allow children under the age of thirteen to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information through the Site.
  * Because we do not collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen as part of the Site, we do NOT condition the participation of a child under thirteen in the Site’s online activities on providing personally identifiable information.

### **How do we store your information?**

Your information is stored at the list server that delivers our content and messaging. Your information can only be accessed by those who help manage those lists in order to deliver e-mail to those who would like to receive our material.

All of the messaging or emails that are sent to you by us include an unsubscribe link in them. You can remove yourself at any time from our mailing list by clicking on the unsubscribe link that can be found in every communication that we send you.

**Security of your Personal Information**

TheTappingSolution.com secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. TheTappingSolution.com secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to trusted partner Web sites for purposes such as processing an order, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

### **Changes to this Statement**

TheTappingSolution.com will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. TheTappingSolution.com encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how TheTappingSolution.com is protecting your information.

### **Contact Information**

TheTappingSolution.com welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that TheTappingSolution.com has not adhered to this Statement, please contact TheTappingSolution.com ([Click here](http://thetappingsolution.com/contact/)). We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
